(Penny:)Okay, everybody,
(Penny:)Sheldon is gonna come back out,
(Penny:)but I think
he's a little embarrassed,
(Penny:)so let's all be
extra nice, okay?
(Barry:)What are you
looking at me for?
I'm a saint. (chuckles)
(Barry:)But a sinner in the sack.
(Sheldon:)Hello, everyone.
I-I...
(Sheldon:)I'd like to apologize
for my behavior.
(Sheldon:)I hope it hasn't put
a damper on the party.
So, just, please,
enjoy yourselves.
That's good.
(party chatter resumes)
(Sheldon:)Oh, this is quickly
getting out of hand.
(Amy:)If I may,
I-I'd like to propose a toast.
(Amy:)Um, thank you all
for coming tonight.
(Amy:)I know it's customary
(Amy:)for the birthday boy
to receive presents,
(Amy:)but I feel like I got
the greatest gift
(Amy:)the day he was born.
ALL:
Aw.
Hear, hear.
KOOTHRAPPALI: Cheers.
(Sheldon:)Amy, that was lovely.
(Sheldon:)You know,
(Sheldon:)this is fun.
(Sheldon:)Let's do more.
(Sheldon:)Someone else say something
wonderful about me.